<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="deneme.css"?>
<seo>
    <introduction>
        <description>
            SEO (search engine optimization acronyms) are all techniques or actions aimed at increasing the traffic of a website thanks to improving its positioning in the different search engines (especially Google, the king of search engines, but also others such as Bing or Yahoo). Its main objective is to increase visibility; what's the same, that more visits come to a website.
        </description>
        <importance>
            <history>
                In the beginning, all web page administrators had to do was send the address of a web page, or URL, to the different engines, which would send a web spider or web crawler to inspect that site, extract links to other pages that had that website and return the collected information to be indexed. The process involves a web spider belonging to the search engine, which downloads a page and stores it on the company's servers, where a second program, known as an indexer, extracts information about the page. Among it, the words it contains and where they are located, the relevance of specific words and all the links contained in the page, which are stored to be later tracked by the web spider. The birth of Google, in 1998, changed this and so what we know as SEO was born. Factors external to the page (PageRank and link analysis) were considered as internal factors (keyword frequency, meta tags, headers, links and website structure, page loading speed), to allow Google to avoid type of manipulation seen in search engines that only considered internal factors of the page for classifications.
            </history>
            <present>
                In the last decade, Google Instant, real-time search, has been of great importance in an attempt to make the search results more relevant and recent. Historically, web administrators have spent months or even years optimizing a website to improve its positioning. With the rise in popularity of social media and blogs, major engines made changes to their algorithms to allow for fresh content and quickly position search results. In addition, Google implemented the "Panda" update, which penalizes websites that contain duplicate content from other sites and sources. Historically, web pages have copied content from others benefiting from the classification of search engines by applying this technique, however Google implemented a new system in which it penalizes web pages whose content is not unique. Also the "Penguin" update aimed at penalizing those sites that used manipulative techniques to improve their rankings. (SEO Spam or Web Spam).
            </present>
            <future>
                The future is difficult to predict, but the most immediate goes through voice assistants that allow users to perform an Internet search when asking a question verbally. Some of the best known are: Alexa, Siri, Google Now and Cortana. These can be controlled via a smartphone and also be present in our home by voice devices, such as Amazon Echo, even integrated into a Smart TV. The increase in this search methodology, from the SEO point of view, means that we should focus on thinking about the intent of the user's voice search. We must bear in mind that people do not speak the same way we write, that searches that are carried out through verbal communication are longer and more natural phrases than those we use in written communication. This brings about a radical change in implementing an SEO strategy. It means that we will go from conducting a traditional keyword study focused on searching as a traditional user would on their pc or mobile, to performing a Search Intent Voice. The use of long tail in SEO will become more relevant due to their use in conversational searches.
            </future>
        </importance>
    </introduction>
    <use>
        <searchEngines>
            <introduction>
                As noted above, Internet search engines are the fundamental field of work for SEO tools. At this point we will analyze the most important ones.
            </introduction>
            <principalEngines>
                    <Google>
                        Larry Page and Sergey Brin met at Stanford University in 1995, while pursuing a doctorate in computer science.
                        As part of their research project, Page and Brin began developing BackRub, a new system for sorting search engine results.
                        The first version of Google was released in August 1996, on a website owned by Stanford (google.stanford.edu).
                        It was such a colossal project that it used nearly half the bandwidth of the university's network. Finally, in September 1997 they registered the domain google.com.
                        That's when entrepreneurs and investors, and not just researchers, started to take an interest in Google.
                        In August 2004 Google went public and since then, investors from all over the world can buy shares of the company.
                        Even today the founders Page and Brin retain 14% of the shares and control more than half of the voting power.
                        After the IPO, the value of the company increased very quickly and, to this day, it is this search engine that marks the SEO strategies that users follow.
                        All other search engines have no choice but to adapt.
                    </Google>
                    <Yahoo>
                        In 1994, in their busy makeshift office at Stanford University, Jerry Yang and David Filo created a kind of directory of web pages that facilitated the search for information from that archaic internet of the late 20th century.
                        By the end of 1994, the directory already exceeded 100,000 visits per day. In 1995, they created the yahoo.com domain.
                        Yang and Filo immediately saw the commercial potential of their product and, after getting a venture capital firm to invest $1 million in Yahoo, began trying their luck at a multitude of services still incipient.
                        In 1996, the company began trading on the stock exchange. From there, between constant acquisitions and new businesses, everything went up: the creation of Yahoo!
                        Mail, the opening of its playground, the acquisition of GeoCities, the premiere of Yahoo! Groups and Yahoo! Messenger...
                        That said, the concatenation of failures and bad business decisions led Yahoo to which in 2017, 23 years after its creation, it will be totally disintegrated, with its most popular services held by Verizon.
                    </Yahoo>
                    <Bing>
                        Bing (formerly Live Search, Windows Live Search, and MSN Search) is a Microsoft web browser.
                        Presented by former Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer on May 28, 2009 at the All Things Digital conference in San Diego, it was brought online on June 3, 2009 with a preview released on June 1, 2009.
                        Some of its most important and competitively differentiating developments were the list of real-time search suggestions and a list of related searches, based on Powerset3 semantic technology that Microsoft purchased in 2008.
                        On July 29, 2009, Microsoft and Yahoo! announced that Bing would replace Yahoo! Search. This change was implemented in early 2012.
                    </Bing>
                    <others>
                        Although the above are by far the most used search engines in the world today, there are others that also have some importance.
                        For example, Baidu, Ask, Aol Search, DuckDuckGo, WolframAlpha, Yandex, WebCrawler, Search, dogpile, ixquick, excite and Info.
                    </others>
            </principalEngines>
        </searchEngines>
        <optimization>
            <introduction>
                SEO optimization is a set of techniques in order to improve the natural or organic (non-paid) results of a particular website or blog in the results of Google and other search engines.
                The three concepts to consider here are: the user experience, the quality of the content and the authority of the site.
            </introduction>
            <keyWords>
                A keyword (also called SEO words) is the text that a user enters into Google to search for information.
                <use>
                    When a search engine user hits the search button, the search engine gives you results in relation to the keyword that the person has entered.
                    An easy way to understand what keywords are is to imagine them as questions that people ask Google and that he answers through the contents that exist on the Internet.
                </use>
            </keyWords>
            <friendlyUrl>
                <use>
                    Friendly UrLs, also known as semantic Urls, are those addresses that are easy for users to understand thanks to their structure and shape.
                    They move away from the classics, also known as dynamics, because they do not incorporate strange signs or numbering, always trying to throw key information so that anyone can understand the content they host on the page they are directing to.
                </use>
            </friendlyUrl>
            <title>
                <use>
                    An SEO title is, like titles in general, the primary person in charge of communicating and presenting a theme,
                    with the difference that appears in search engines and has an additional purpose that is to help position and invite readers to enter a certain Content.
                </use>
            </title>
            <description>
                <use>
                    The meta description tag is an important factor in getting visits to your website. This is the information that appears in Google results that explains what that person will be found on your site if they click.
                    The meta description is the space offered by Google to capture the user's attention and differentiate yourself from the rest of the results, that is, from the competitors. This label should be attractive, relevant.
                </use>
            </description>
            <tags>
                <use>
                    Meta tags or meta tags are typically used to summarize page content for search engines and web browsers. That is, they describe the page so that it can be understood by different web services.
                    There are also meta tags designed to tell robots how you want the page to be treated. Because the information is directed at machines, meta tags are not visible to the user.
                    They are set in the HTML code of the page, within the &#60;Head&#62; section. The most popular meta tags are description and keywords, although there are others such as robots, author and generator, among others.
                </use>
            </tags>
            <linkProfile>
                <use>
                    Link profile is the set of external links that a website receives, also called backlinks. More simple, all those that link to a website.
                    Within these links are those that are left in comments, those that are put when you participate in other blogs, those that someone leaves in forums, etc.
                </use>
            </linkProfile>
            <images>
                <use>
                    Basically, it is about uploading the images to a website in the best possible way in front of Google, mainly taking into account the optimization of the weight of the image to make it as small as possible,
                    the definition in its "alt" attribute of what the image is going, the name of the image file itself and not committing with them any kind of practice unfriendly to search engines.
                </use>
            </images>
        </optimization>
    </use>
    <types>
        <onpage>
            <description>
                SEO On Page refers to optimizations that can be made on a website to improve its organic positioning. That is, everything that depends directly on the administrator, since it is the one that controls the web.
                The goal of SEO On Page is to make life easy for Google, so you can index pages as quickly as possible... and classify them according to the user's interest.
            </description>
        </onpage>
        <offpage>
            <description>
                SEO off page are all SEO actions that are used off-web with the aim of improving their ranking in search engines; it's about everything that's done externally to increase the authority of a website.
                It's not just about building backlinks or backlinks, but also about all promotions that are made from a web page, even if this doesn't include a link as such. SeO off page can make a difference.
                Sii two similar websites, working in the same niche, have an excellent PLAN of SEO On Page, the best ranked in search engines will be decided by SEO off page.
            </description>
        </offpage>
        <BHS>
            <description>
                This is a set of unethical practices for achieving instant results. The goal is to improve the position in Google's ranking on the results pages of specific keywords.
                By doing the opposite you can get the same results, but in a long period of time and respecting the rules imposed by Google.
                However, exceeding the limits imposed by the search engine to display a page in SERPs can have disastrous consequences. Black Hat SEO is effective in a short time,
                but as soon as Google detects the deception, it will not only lower the site's positioning, but may eventually disappear from the results page.
            </description>
            <examples>
                <Cloaking>
                    It is a cheating technique as what is shown to the browser is not the same as shown to users. It consists of misleading Google, making it believe that your page is optimized, when it really isn't.
                    Users are directed to a page that has not been tracked by search engines. An example of this is so-called flash pages. That is, the contents differ depending on whether it is viewed by a robot or a user.
                </Cloaking>
                <KeywordStuffing>
                    This is an unethical, simple and very popular practice. Keyword stuffing basically consists of repeatedly using a single word.
                    If you do it a couple of times, nothing will happen. The problem lies in excesses. Google is clear on this issue of keywords and SEO positioning.
                    You can use the keyword, as long as it responds to the needs of the users and provides a value. The use of these meaningless keywords that only confuse the user is severely penalized by the search engine.
                </KeywordStuffing>
                <Spinning>
                    Consists of creating new articles based on originals. This means that even if it is not copied in its entirety, it is mimicking text that already exists. And Google doesn't like that either.
                    This practice is based on the idea of reusing texts by changing words or ordering phrases. These modifications manage to generate content quickly and easily.
                    It also manages to deceive the user, making him believe that these are novel content. There is software that allows to automate this process, facilitating the work of modifying the words.
                    But it is also possible to do it manually, more natural and believable for the reader. The first is heavily penalized by Google.
                </Spinning>
            </examples>
        </BHS>
        <WHS>
            <description>
                White Hat Seo is a set of ethically acceptable techniques aimed at positioning a website correctly and fully accepted by Google. This is the work totally opposed to Black Hat SEO.
            </description>
            <examples>
                <QualityContent>
                    No copying, no re-writing, no changing a few words. Content creation is an art and, above all, an art that is measured by quality, not quantity.
                    You have to offer a text without ramblings, explanatory and deep, without useless content to reach a number of words.
                </QualityContent>
                <LongTail>
                    One of the best White hat techniques for positioning is to go from least to too. That is, bet on keywords with fewer searches, but also less competitive,
                    because these URLs will position more easily and that is very good. They don't provide a lot of monthly visits, but they'll signal Google,
                    which also indicates that these keywords are also part of our niche.
                </LongTail>
                <SolidLinkbuilding>
                    Getting natural and quality links is a complicated task. That's why sometimes it's very easy to fall into spam to avoid paying for good links.
                    Google is getting smarter and understands when links aren't natural. A professional and quality link-building strategy must be used.
                </SolidLinkbuilding>
                <Youtube>
                    There are several ways and several hacks that are being used to position videos in Google's ranking. If the video is widely shared and has good SEO on-page,
                    you can position the URL, as well as position yourself on video in the Google ranking. So you can go out twice in the top positions in the same search.
                    The key is on the embed. If there are pages with the video of the web, Google will know that that video is something very relevant and therefore will show it in the first positions.
                </Youtube>
            </examples>
        </WHS>
    </types>
</seo>
